Yajaira Nicole Argueta Sibrian

Currently student of Computing System Engeneering at Universidad de El Salvador with knowledge of English and Computing thanks to ¡Supérate! Scholarship where I was learning the language for 3 years (2019 - 2021). Looking forward to growing and obtaining experience in the working world putting my skills into practice.



PERSONAL INFORMATION

- San Salvador, October 16, 2003
- Comunidad El Paraíso Meléndez Casa #5, contiguo a Sierra Morena, Soyapango.
- 🔽 arguetayajaira17@gmail.com
- Mobile: 6997-6687

EDUCATION

• Centro Escolar Reino de "Dinamarca"

CATERING AND TOURISM SPECIALIZATION 2020-2021

• Centro Escolar Colonia "Las Brisas"

ELEMENTARY EDUCATION 2011-2019

C O M P L E M E N T A R Y S T U D I E S

• Centro ¡Supérate! ADOC

ENGLISH, COMPUTER AND LIFE SKILLS SPECIALIZATION
JANUARY 2019- DECEMBER 2021

LANGUAGES

English Centro ¡Supérate! ADOC

- 3 years (2019-2021)
- Advanced level
- TOEIC L&R Certification (825 score)
- TOEIC S&W Certification (310 score)

AWARDS OBTAINED

Centro ¡Supérate! ADOC

- 6 integral recognitions (2019-2021)
- Integrity Award (2021)
- Silver award TOEIC Listening and Reading (2021)
- Silver award TOEIC Speaking and Writing (2021)

WORK EXPERIENCE

- Management of entrepreneurship "Moon Bisuteria". 2019- 2024
- -Content creation Creation of merchandise
- -Dealing with customers Delivery arrangements

VOLUNTEERING

 Volunteer in Central American and Caribbean Games 2023

JUNE 2023-JULY 2023

Support in the lodging and hotel area with my english skills, assisting the players and staff members of each of the teams, solving doubts regarding their stay and guiding them through the daily agenda.

- Volunteer in the organization "Volunteers" ¡Supérate! 2019
- -Nursing home "San Vicente de Paul"
- -Cunas de Carton





SKILLS

CONTESTS / COMPETITIONS

- Responsibility
- Adaptability
- Patience
- Time Management
- Conflict Resolution
- Teamwork
- Assertive communication
- Creativity

COMPUTING

- Office technology
- Design
- HTML and CSS tag language
- Windows operating system
- Microsoft Office 365 integrated packages
- Certification in Microsoft Excel 2016
- Microsoft Technology Associate (MTA certification)

Centro ¡Supérate! ADOC

- Second place group in General Culture 2019
- One of the best web pages of the class

Centro Escolar Colonia "Las Brisas"

- Spelling Bee
- Poetry competition
- Student pageant